[Never-Ending Summer]
[Episode 28]
Come back to me
just like when we were kids, okay?
So, today,
you came to me
to make a deal with me?
Of course, no.
I just want you to see me.
What if I say I don't want to?
Jiang Yan.
I love Lu Xixiao
not because he helped me.
I don't need to
give him something in return
for him doing anything for me.
If you
give me the evidence
just to threaten me
into making a choice,
now you know the answer.
Why?
Since we were kids,
since the very beginning,
and since ten years ago,
I told you many times that
I sincerely treated you
as my good friend.
And I
trusted you.
I know that in the accident ten years ago,
it was you who leaked my whereabouts
to Luo He.
But I still believe
you didn't mean it.
Few people knew
I went back to Pingchuan.
I just don't understand why,
even though you know how important
the matter of Director Wang is to me,
you utilize it
to force me to leave Lu Xixiao.
I...
Let's go our separate ways from now on.
Finished talking with Jiang Yan?
The communication didn't go well?
I might not be able to get
the evidence in Jiang Yan's hand.
It's okay.
I found the dealer
who coordinated with Director Wang.
If we have a way
to let him tell the truth,
everything will be fine.
Let's go to him tomorrow.
There's no reward?
What?
You went to see my rival in love
and left me alone
for an hour.
Shouldn't you reward me?
You insisted on coming here.
I don't care.
I'm jealous.
Coax me.
Is it okay?
Stop it.
Go home.
Yes, Ma'am.
I asked you to supervise
the Phase II project.
Why am I the last one
to know about the incident of
Shengshi Huayu?
When I heard the news,
it had already happened.
Why didn't you report to me
at the first time?
Don't you know that Xinghai Entertainment
was introduced by me?
As Shengshi Huayu got involved,
Xinghai Entertainment
would be abandoned.
I remember that
you told me
you needed me, an experienced person,
to take charge of the Phase II project
on behalf of the headquarters.
If anything goes wrong,
I should report to the headquarters.
Based on my experience,
I didn't think
there was anything wrong.
On the contrary,
it will also add to the project.
You've learned to
play the word game with me, huh?
I helped you
get this position.
I can also make you step down.
Mr. Lu,
please help yourself.
Do you still think
I'm the kid who was threatened by you
with several words and at your disposal?
Wait.
My boy,
listen to me.
You're my son.
You are much better
than Lu Xixiao.
Since you treated me like this,
I believe you will do the same to others.
You inherited from me.
If you keep doing this,
one day,
you will make great achievements.
Trust me, baby.
Baby.
Mr. Lu.
Well...
What is it?
Someone saw Xixiao and Zhou Wan
go to Wang Yongli's house together.
Damn it.
Both of the two brats
are
going against me.
Fine.
Zhou Wan is trying to
figure out
what happened back then.
Well...
As for the incident of Yinshan Factory...
I don't need you to remind me of that!
Dad, don't go.
Didn't he promise to help us?
You don't have to hide, right?
The matter hasn't been resolved yet.
I don't want to drag you down.
Take good care of Grandma
and study hard.
Wang Yongli.
Finally, you're home.
Now, you have money
to pay your debt, right?
Give me some more time.
I...
I have no money.
No money? No money?
What's your excuse this time?
Do you think I still trust you?
Lan Yue's men came to you
and gave you food and drinks.
Selling the factory land
must have made you a lot of money, right?
Lan Yue's men?
-Don't play dumb!
-Let go!
Let him go.
[Lan Yue Group, B2]
You've been in the toilet for so long.
The information company sent me
the address.
I'll wait for you in the garage.
Li Xin talked with me just now.
I'm in the elevator.
I'll go downstairs now.
Okay. There's no rush.
Do you want to go there after dinner
or right now?
Go there right now.
Hello?
Hello, Zhou Wan.
Zhou Wan. Hello?
Get the three elevators' surveillance
on the first floor of Building A.
[CCTV]
Hurry up!
These three.
Zoom in.
[CCTV]
[Elevator 8]
Let's go.
It's him!
Director Lu, do you know him?
[CCTV]
The police will be here soon.
Tell them
this person is Wang Yongli.
He was
the director of
Yinshan Furniture Factory.
When the police arrive,
ask them to search
the surroundings of the Jinsha Bay
and Yinshan Furniture Factory.
[CCTV]
Director Lu.
Aren't you waiting for the police?
Where are you going?
[Elevator 8]
Did something happen?
Get out of my sight.
Did something happen to Zhou Wan?
How dare you ask me this question?
Wang Yongli took Zhou Wan away.
It's all your fault.
Get in. I'll go with you.
There are not many places
where Wang Yongli can hide.
I've checked.
He was hiding in
the old building of Yinshan Factory.
I know where it is. Hurry up!
Lu Xixiao,
as for Luo He's incident ten years ago,
I'm sorry.
I cared too much about
my family background.
That's why I keep making mistakes.
What's wrong with you?
Why are you telling me this now?
I hated Lu Zhongyue
and resented you.
But it doesn't matter now.
Let bygones be bygones.
If you hadn't wasted the time
saying these words to me,
we would be there now.
Jiang Yan,
you've loved Zhou Wan
for so many years.
Have you ever
protected her even once?
Listen.
If anything happens to Zhou Wan today,
you'll never be able to repay it.
Yes, it's my fault.
I just can't
accept that
you are always prior to me
in everyone's eyes.
You have a better background.
Zhou Wan loves you.
Grandpa values you.
Even Lu Zhongyue
thinks highly of you.
But I never meant
-to hurt Zhou Wan.
-Enough.
Stop talking nonsense.
Can you just drive?
Lu Xixiao.
There are many buildings here.
Let's split up.
You're awake.
Do you know what this place is?
Yinshan Furniture Factory
moved to Jinsha Bay.
The factory you founded
was
near the raw material production site.
You know what?
Back then,
I bought this land
and made
every piece of furniture
together with my men.
Then, we had the opportunity to
expand the business.
Later,
I bought this place.
But then,
I got a failure
and ended up like this.
I can only hide here.
And all this
is Lu Zhongyue's fault.
I understand.
I totally understand.
Lili must have told you
what happened to me.
Lu Zhongyue used the same trick
to frame my dad's factory,
causing my dad's bankruptcy
and leaving him with a huge debt.
Later, my dad
died of depression.
Director Wang,
I really want to help you.
That's like
helping my father.
Stop lying.
I know
you are a member of
Lan Yue Group.
That day,
the one who followed you to my home
was Lu Zhongyue's son.
Now,
do you have any more excuses?
If you really want to help me,
let me ask you.
Where is the evidence
I gave you?
I can explain it.
I can also
get it back.
I promise you.
It's too late.
Do you think I'll trust you again?
That evidence
might be
in Lu Zhongyue's hands.
I have nothing now.
Director Wang, calm down.
Think about it.
You have Lili.
Let's help the factory
get back to normal.
Shut up!
Director Wang! Director Wang!
Listen.
You don't deserve to
mention my daughter's name.
I have prepared
the evidence.
and written my suicide note.
I believe the police will be able to
find out what Lu Zhongyue has done!
Zhou Wan!
Stop! Don't come over!
You must be Lu Zhongyue's son.
You came just in time.
I will let Lu Zhongyue taste
the feelings of losing everything.
Calm down.
Director Wang,
please calm down and think it over.
I'm Lu Zhongyue's son.
If you need anything,
you can threaten him
with me.
Hurting Zhou Wan
is no help
to you now.
Think about your mother.
Think about Lili.
Let Lan Yue explain
the incident of the furniture factory
for you.
You don't have to hide anymore.
Your mom and daughter can live
a safe and sound life.
As long as you don't hurt Zhou Wan,
I can cooperate with you
to do anything.
I'll do anything you ask me to do.
Let me see her first.
Let me know she's safe.
Okay?
Alright.
It's useless to say this.
Don't come over!
Turn around.
Turn around!
Put both hands behind your back!
Zhou Wan!
Are you okay?
-Are you hurt?
-Are you okay?
How dare you fool me?
I shouldn't have trusted you!
Go to hell together!
Let's end everything
and see who can survive
and live a good life.
How are you?
Are you hurt?
None of you can escape!
Are you okay?
Your arm...
I'm fine.
I was just in time.
Thanks.
Recently,
Wang, the owner of
Yinshan Furniture Factory,
was arrested for kidnapping.
Wang claimed that his factory
went bankrupt
due to malicious competition.
The police are currently
investigating related cases.
Don't move.
Stay still.
No, my legs are too long.
I can't stretch.
I mean your arm.
Be careful
when you take a shower.
Don't let the wound get wet.
I can't guarantee that.
Because I hurt my right arm.
Your arm is not broken.
I've sealed it for you.
Everything will be fine.
Turn around.
Seems your injury
is completely fine.
I worried for nothing.
How is that possible?
My arm
still hurts.
Put your hand down.
Who made you do...
That's because you're good at bandaging.
My wound
didn't get wet.
Really.
My arm is still…
It's just a lift that I…
Why didn't you stop moving your arm?
You're acting again.
Hey.
-Do you want me to blow-dry your hair?
-It hurts. It hurts.
-Ouch!
-I'll stop right now.
I need you to blow-dry my hair.
Continue. Continue, please.
-No.
-Continue, please.
Let's stop here.
I'm impatient.
Don't leave.
I have something to tell you.
Are you going to...
No.
I have something to tell you.
Really.
Go ahead.
Wang Yongli
is now facing criminal charges.
But he can still
sue Lan Yue.
And
I've found
more evidence of
the incident of Yinshan Furniture Factory.
Together with the evidence
Jiang Yan left,
the truth of
the Yinshan Furniture Factory
will be revealed, right?
There's a piece of bad news.
The supplier who cheated your dad,
whose surname is Huo,
died in a car accident.
So, it means
we have no clue here.
Even if we can
win the lawsuit,
we still can't prove
what Lu Zhongyue did to your dad.
I know it's hard
to hold someone accountable
for my dad's tragedy.
But it's okay
as long as Lu Zhongyue's misconduct
can be exposed.
It's me.
I saw the news.
Let's meet.
You've changed a lot.
You are mature.
This is the coffee I ordered for you.
What do you want from me?
I have nothing
to talk to you.
This is for you.
Take a look.
You've been working hard
[About Jun'an Building Materials Factory]
for so many years
[and
Hengguan Hardware
and Building Materials Co., Ltd]
for this, right?
[Correspondence and Handling Records
Regarding Raw Material Quality Disputes]
I handled all these at that time.
There is some evidence
left by the material factory
and dealers.
I just wanted
to leave myself a way out.
Now, I don't need it anymore.
I've thought a lot these years.
I want to live a different life.
Why did you help me?
I didn't expect you
to keep investigating the truth.
I always thought
we were the same kind of people.
But
I just figured it out now that
scheming everything
and trying your best
are different.
You are doing well now,
better than me.
Good.
My daughter, may you be happy.
I'll let you pay the bill.
You're welcome.
You really don't need me to go with you?
Didn't we agree that?
It's related to the Lu family.
I don't want to make you uncomfortable.
Well,
I'll wait for you at home.
This matter
has caused a stir,
creating a bad influence
on our company.
Someone has to be responsible
for this.
Mr. Lu,
to be precise,
it was because of
the malicious intent of the acquisition
of Yinshan Furniture Factory.
Xixiao and the others
went to do a routine inspection
but suffered extreme revenge.
No matter what,
they should not
be blamed.
Don't you think
you're beating around the bush?
As for the incident of
Yinshan Furniture Factory,
there are some tumors.
How could a villain's words
be credible?
That's just slander from
a desperate man.
But those who in charge of the project
of the company
disregarded the company's interests
and acted without permission,
causing such a big trouble.
I suggest we dismiss them
as soon as possible.
Mr. Lu, don't bother.
I'll resign right now.
This is the meeting of
the board of directors.
You're not qualified
to attend the meeting.
I invited Miss Zhou
especially
as the witness of the incident.
Let's listen to
what she wants to say.
What do you think?
What do you mean?
-This is the meeting of...
-Mr. Lu.
When senior Mr. Lu
heard this incident,
he was very angry.
He asked me
to hold a board meeting immediately.
I think
he wants to hear
the story from the person involved.
Mr. Lu,
what do you think?
[Meeting of Chairman No.78
of Lan Yue Group]
I'm sorry.
I can't continue to be in charge of
the Phase II project of Lan Yue.
Sorry for making trouble
for you and Ms. Qilan.
Before I leave,
I have sent two important documents
to you
via email.
Please check them.
[Yinshan Furniture Quality Issue]
The first one
is the evidence of
[Yinshan Furniture Quality Issue]
sabotaging business operations
and conducting contract fraud
in the process of purchasing
the land
of the Phase II project of Lan Yue.
Before Yinshan Furniture Factory
was acquired,
the factory director, Wang Yongli,
[Yinshan Furniture Quality Issue]
was sued
for using inferior products,
and then, the factory closed down.
But in fact,
[Yinshan Furniture Quality Issue]
it was because the purchaser of
Yinshan Furniture Factory
and the dealers
who provided raw materials
colluded secretly
to forge the quality inspection report,
leading to
product quality issues.
Thus, Wang Yongli
was forced to transfer the land
to Lan Yue at a very low price.
Cut the crap.
What nonsense are you talking about?
-Mr. Lu.
-You must...
Behave yourself.
Have a seat.
Coincidentally,
[Yinshan Furniture Quality Issue]
you did the same thing
[Product Quality Issue
of Jun'an Construction]
20 years ago.
Do you remember
Jun'an Building Materials Factory?
During the purchase of the land of
Lan Yue Phase I project of the resort,
Lu Zhongyue set up a trap with the dealer
in the same way,
causing Jun'an's bankruptcy.
In this way, it was purchased
by Lan Yue at a low price.
For 20 years,
many families
have been
driven to destitution,
and ruined
due to you.
I know, for you,
it's just
a dirty deal.
But for people
who experienced all this,
they've waited for the truth
for 20 years.
The materials in your hands
have also been sent
to relevant departments.
I believe someone will
come to investigate it.
Lan Yue is a leading enterprise
in Pingchuan.
I believe its development
relies on upholding integrity
in operations
and putting people first.
I believe all of you
will make a proper choice
for the long-term development
of Lan Yue.
[Product Quality Issue
of Jun'an Construction]
By the way, Mr. Lu,
do you remember
the name of the director
of Jun'an Building Materials Factory?
His name is Zhou Jun.
Dad.
Lu Zhongyue has been punished
by the law.
The truth
is finally revealed.
♪ Fast footsteps ♪
♪ When we just stepped out,
we didn't meet ♪
♪ Yet already in impatience ♪
♪ In the air after the rain ♪
♪ Everything is filled with joy ♪
[Lan Yue Group]
♪ Your whisper ♪
♪ Is in sync with ♪
♪ My breath ♪
♪ You seem to have heard ♪
♪ The unspoken loneliness ♪
♪ And the feelings I dare not say ♪
♪ Let me sink into the time
when you are here ♪
♪ This world is always too cruel ♪
♪ With you here,
I can honestly admit my expectations ♪
♪ Beyond what I had imagined ♪
Xixiao, I told you
she is not the right fit for you.
Why are you
so stubborn?
Grandpa,
you should know
I'm different from Lu Zhongyue.
I don't need someone like my mom
to be with me,
and guide me every day
to keep me on the right path.
All I've done these years
has proved it.
I've grown up.
I can call the shots
in my life.
I don't care about
others' opinions and comments.
So, you don't have to
threaten her with these things
and force her to put herself in my shoes.
I know what I want.
I also know
what I can do.
This matter
is between us.
I was young, immature,
and childish. I had no say.
So, I had no choice.
But whether I forgive her now
or not
depends on me.
The agreement you made with her
doesn't count anymore.
You told her not to show up
in front of me anymore
but never asked about my opinions.
Grandpa,
it's not fair.
You've always had a keen eye for people.
It's not simply a matter
of whether two people
are right for each other
or not.
Look at my mom and Lu Zhongyue.
If they had
divorced,
all these tragedies
wouldn't have happened.
I really hope
the Lu family
can be warmer.
So, grandpa,
what I want to tell you
is very simple.
I only have feelings with Zhou Wan.
All these years,
she is my only love.
She made me feel
the world
is interesting.
So, except for her,
I don't want anyone.
From the very beginning,
she had ulterior motives.
She utilized you.
Don't you care about that?
I don't care.
I told you.
As long as I am with her,
no matter what difficulties
and setbacks I will encounter,
I will accept them.
Let me do it.
Sit down.
Have some tea.
Jiang Fan, open the door.
The agent called me.
He said you didn't answer his calls
or hand over the house to him.
What do you want to do?
Open the door!
It is my first time visiting a house.
-It’s so big.
-Do you like it?
This is exactly
my dream kitchen.
We can place
a six-person table here.
Then, when Wan
and my parents come here,
they can eat here.
Okay.
Let's
put a wine cabinet here.
Honey.
I also want to
put the dolls in the cabinet.
[Filming]
Okay.
The TV wall is so big.
Don't install a TV.
-Let's install...
-A projection screen.
I know.
I'll edit all the materials
we filmed
and show the videos on the screen.
[Filming]
You're clever.
But I don't like the curtains.
Honey,
I would like to change the curtains
to warm colors.
Cream-colored ones, okay?
Let's buy
all the warm colors.
Okay. Cream-colored ones are okay.
It feels warm.
[Filming]
And here.
I want to buy an eight-person big sofa,
so our dogs can lie here.
The walls will be covered
all our old photos
since childhood.
I'm so happy.
But it's too big.
I love you, honey. I love you.
Jiang Fan, I love you so much!
I love you, Jiang Fan.
Why are you so nice?
Honey, I love you. I love you.
I love you too, honey.
[Filming]
I love you.
Honey.
I used to think that
as long as I make more money
and become better,
and improve
the quality of our life,
we will live a happy life
forever.
I thought our relationship
would never change
and we'd never separate
after we got married.
But now I know
marriage is just the beginning
of our relationship.
I'm sorry.
I haven't cared about you
for a long time.
I haven't looked at you
like this for a long time.
But trust me.
Every day in the future,
I will
prioritize you.
Can you give me another chance?
Does your leg hurt?
No.
I'll say yes if you say it hurts.
So, your answer is yes?
♪ Countless, unforgettable ♪
♪ No time left, so I ♪
♪ Can only fall toward you ♪
♪ Too dazzling, too lonely, it's alright ♪
♪ I believe in this encounter ♪
♪ Landing in the ruins of the galaxy ♪
♪ Exchanging our comets ♪
♪ Suddenly I am certain ♪
♪ This mud all over me ♪
Do you have anything else to say?
♪ Is the proof of love ♪
Do you have
anything else to say?
After Xixiao's art exhibition is finished,
I'll take a long vacation.
I'll go with you
wherever you want.
No.
I want to let you stay here
and never leave.
♪ I can't remember and can't go back ♪
Okay.
Let's stay at home
♪ If you can't hold it tightly, let me ♪
until we get moldy.
♪ Fly without hesitation ♪
We'll stay here
and hide our tracks
from everyone.
♪ Sorry, I'm too capricious and obsessed ♪
♪ The Milky Way is drowning ♪
Let's get moldy together.
♪ If one day you fall into ♪
Yes.
♪ The gap a light-year away ♪
That's what I like about you.
♪ You'll find ♪
I'm glad you like it.
♪ The scattered ashes ♪
♪ Burns my heart ♪